

SWANN MARTIN

CONTACT INFO

₹ 1030 Schaerbeek

☐ Tél: +32 456 59 60 82

M <u>swannmartin1988@gmail.com</u>

Portfolio: <u>swannmartin.xyz</u>

@swann.martin

https://github.com/swann-martin

■ <u>Driving Licence & car</u>

Fluent in English, French Native Speaker

PROFILE

Front-End developer specialised in TypeScript, I can develop React, React Native, Angular and Ionic 6 apps. I am used to work with agile method and scrum. I use jira, office 360, and git daily. I have worked for years in an English speaking context.

PROJECTS https://github.com/swann-martin

WashatHome

Use React, Redux, axios, Leaflet, node, sass

Burger Shop:

Use React, useState

Sofas:

Use React, React-Router, Sass

Portfolio:

Use React, React-Router, Sass

Weather app:

Flutter, OpenWeather Api

CV Generator:

Symfony, twig, jQuery, CSS

HOBBIES



Climbing



GNU Linux,



Fantasy,SF



FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

SKILLS

React/ Native























Other

Main

Secondary

Back-end









Organised, Rigourous, Flexible, Reactive, Curious Can do attitude, Decisive

EXPERIENCE

[</>] FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Beecoming | Decembre 2021 - Today

- Developping apps in React Native, Ionic 6/ Angular & React.js
- TypeScript, NodeJS, Prestashop, Socket.io
- Agile, Scrum, Git, Jira, Office 360



SALES REPRESENTATIVE LANGUAGE COURSE

Oxford Intensive School of English | 2014 - 2020

- Managing a booking office in Bordeaux & Lille
- Bookings Average Annual Income 250 000€
- Organized, work in English and French, management

TRAINING

O'CLOCK:

Formation React.JS | Juin 2021 - Août 2021

Training in React.js, Redux.

End of training project de fin de formation : A website to rent your washing machine for money.

Technologies: React, Redux, Node, postGreSql

WEBFORCE 3 BORDEAUX

Certification Dev Web | Jan 2021 - Avril 2021

Certifications professionnelles CNCP (catégorie C):

- Techniques d'intégration Web (front-end) : (HTML / CSS, JavaScript / jQuery, Angular, CMS: Wordpress)
- Techniques de développement Web (back-end) : (MySQL, PHP, Symfony).

End of training project : CV generator website.

Technologies: Symfony/Twig/SQL/CSS

UNIVERSITY OF PORTSMOUTH / PARIS X

Master2 FLE / PGCE MFL | Sept 2011 - Juin 2013

- Double Diploma Master 2 Teaching Modern Foreign Languages UK

LYCÉE MIREILLE GRENET COMPIEGNE

BACCALAUREAT Sciences Engineering technologies spe Electronics with Honors | 2007